# ABIGAIL MULDERRIG

## CREATIVE DESIGNER

#### CONTACT

07393662571

abigailmulderrig@gmail.com

BT25 Kinallen

### SKILLS

Adobe Creative Cloud

Graphic Design

Videography & Editing

Social Media Content Creation

-----

## EDUCATION

BCS Hons Neurophysiology
Manchester Metropolitan
University

2015 - 2018

Level 3 Applied Medical Science **Burnley College** 

2013 - 2015 D, M, M

Advanced Masterclass in Graphic Design **Udemy** 

2022

Modules include Logo Design, Package Design, Infographics and Brand Identity.

Complete After Effects Bootcamp Udemy

2023

Modules include Motion Graphics, Visual Effects, 3D Motion Graphics and compositing techniques.

## Complete Web Design and Development **Udemy**

Present

Modules include HTML, CSS, Javascript and web design.

#### PROFILE

Ambitious, dedicated and creative individual, who is extremely driven to develop skills and career. Excellent verbal and written communication skills. Well experienced in Adobe Creative Cloud software, particularly Illustrator, Photoshop and Premier Pro. Self-improver, recently completed Udemy masterclasses in Graphic Design and After Effects, also enriching skills with part time freelance work involving brand design and illustration.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Social Media Manager**

Witch Kings Bar & Restaurant September 2023 - February 2024

- Design and schedule creative and engaging content from infographic event reminders to photo and video content for stories and reels.
- Management of social media sites, particularly Facebook, Instagram and TikTok. Adapting content to suit different channels and audiences.
- Audience, industry and analytics research to highlight areas of that are performing well and areas of improvement, tailoring a plan to develop successful promotion strategies.
- Encourage engagement and interaction by responding to all comments and queries.
- Discuss and develop future strategies, potential events and collaborations.
- Working closely with the managers and suppliers to maintain great collaboration and communication for future plans and targets.

## **Junior Designer**

Danielle Group

November 2019 - September 2023

- Creating high quality footwear designs and pattern artwork using Adobe Illustrator, for multiple customers, considering each customers' specific needs in regards to trend direction.
- Active research to stay up to date with new, current and future trends.
- Liaising with senior members, external suppliers and customers.
- Customer account manager for Cotton Traders, with a heavy involvement in Yours Clothing, Sainsburys', JD Williams and Shop Direct.
- Chair client meetings, primarily to strategise and develop plans for upcoming footwear ranges, presenting powerpoint / Canva presentations.
- Photographing and maintaining sample and material libraries.
- Redesigned the product library to improve clarity, efficiency and design.
- · Commended on innovative designs and work ethic.

## ABIGAIL MULDERRIG

## CREATIVE DESIGNER

## CONTACT 07393662571 abigailmulderrig@gmail.com BT25 Kinallen EXPERTISE · Content creation with the use of multiple design software programs, such as Adobe Creative Cloud and Canva. • In-depth platform knowledge and an understanding of audiences and how to tailor language and content. · Creative flair with an attention to detail. · Analytical thinking and problem solving. · Professional and adaptable interpersonal skills. LANGUAGES English French -

## REFERENCES

References available upon request

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Videographer & Editor**

Angel Film NI

May 2017 - August 2019

- Videographer for a highly established wedding videography business working both on site and editing remotely whilst at university.
- Managing my time effectively from planning the shooting schedule, editing timeline and meeting deadlines.
- Mastering the use of cameras and filming equipment, perfecting different shooting techniques and lighting setups.
- Video editing using Premier Pro, Audition and After Effects to create engaging highlight, full feature and marketing films.
- Precise, calm yet authoritative direction when needed, often during high pressure and emotive situations.
- Enquiry generation, sales, content creation, marketing and hosting vendor exhibitions.

#### **Bar tender & Waitress**

Smithy's Bar & Tavern

January 2019 - May 2019

- Working and living in Alpe D'huez in France.
- Delivering quality customer service while catering to diverse customer needs and preferences, especially in a multilingual environment where effective communication is key.
- Excellent time management of hosting multiple tables, taking orders and serving food.
- Working well within a high-pressure and time intensive environment, managing my own tasks and duties while coordinating with the team.

#### **Volunteer Youth Support Worker**

Gorse Hill Studios, Manchester

June 2019 - September 2019

- Volunteer mentor for a Sound and Vision workshop, working with young people to teach them about videography, working on creating a short film.
- Acting as a leader and mentor throughout various classes and activities, finding innovative ways to keep each of the young people engaged and curious.